<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Update on Purple Planetarium</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/topics/update/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Update on Purple Planetarium</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Lulling</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 14:59:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lullinglore.github.io/topics/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Welcome to my blog!</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/welcome-to-my-blog/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 14:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/welcome-to-my-blog/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, Luli here! Welcome to my corner of the internet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This blog is still new and under construction – but it is now 100% functional so I can already start posting!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find art, stories, worldbuilding for the world I&amp;rsquo;m working on, and all sorts of devlogs; I make narrative games but also dabble in a ton of other technical stuff (this website here is one of them – &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; is one gem of a framework *v*).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My old blog&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://lullinglore.tumblr.com/about&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;about page&lt;/a&gt; still does a good job introducing all that, so give it a read if you&amp;rsquo;re interested! Read on for a more technical introduction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-this-place&#34;&gt;What is this place?
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social media never gave me nearly enough customization options, and I&amp;rsquo;m not comfortable keeping my notes on a platform that could vanish anytime; so it was only a matter of time till I decided to make my very own, full-fledged website. And it&amp;rsquo;s not just a website; it&amp;rsquo;s basically (a portion of) my &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://obsidian.md/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Obsidian&lt;/a&gt; vault, with superpowers *w*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So most of the pages here are actually just notes inside my &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL3NaIVgSlAVJKJf37XqEhUduqTBQ2e-sl&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;PKM&lt;/a&gt;, and that includes the world wiki. As I develop my world in the form of articles, the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://lullinglore.github.io/world&#34; &gt;Purpleverse&lt;/a&gt; section will get populated, too. It works the same for the blog; it&amp;rsquo;s actually really nice to be able to write posts from the comfort of my vault.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now the posts look rather plain on the website, but as I get around to it, it&amp;rsquo;ll become something much, much more interconnected and interesting to navigate. All pages already contain a lot of currently hidden metadata, that will eventually be used to display relevant info and list them in all sorts of places – I&amp;rsquo;m really looking forward to implementing all that! Also I have big plans for the world wiki, I&amp;rsquo;d like to make it as immersive and interactive as possible, so stay tuned c:&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously none of this would have ever been possible just on socials (and even Tumblr which is the most customizable option I know), though I&amp;rsquo;ll still be active on &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://lullinglore.tumblr.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Tumblr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://gamejolt.com/invite/lullinglore/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Game Jolt&lt;/a&gt;. Give me a follow if you&amp;rsquo;d like, and if you don&amp;rsquo;t use that, there&amp;rsquo;s still the good old email newsletter option! But don&amp;rsquo;t expect much activity on there for a while, as I need to push out more content first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;widget newsletter-sidebar&#34;&gt;

    &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://lullinglore.substack.com/embed&#34; width=&#34;350&#34; height=&#34;150&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34;
        style=&#34;border:3px solid var(--accent-color); box-shadow: var(--shadow-l3); border-radius: var(--card-border-radius); margin: 0 auto;&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;next-up&#34;&gt;Next up
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;My current focus is on worldbuilding, and more specifically global geography. I aim to get a solid geographical base for my world, and so have completed the rather huge undertaking of simulating the planet&amp;rsquo;s tectonic history. Next is figuring out what kind of land that gives me, aka topography; then will come global climate. Once that&amp;rsquo;s done, I can focus in developing the areas where my stories take place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In parallel, I work on Project Purple, the first narrative game and a &amp;ldquo;short&amp;rdquo; practice project. It&amp;rsquo;s set in my world but to progress as quickly as possible on it, I decided to not wait for the worldbuilding to be completed first; so it&amp;rsquo;s going to use whatever latest version of my world exists in my head, and I expect some things to be retconned later, but it&amp;rsquo;s fine. The story is self-contained and doesn&amp;rsquo;t need much context to work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also in parallel, I might continue working on this website (the visuals and features of it) because it&amp;rsquo;s clearly not up to my standards right now. But hey, I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for it to be perfect before I can use it either. It&amp;rsquo;s good to be messy sometimes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s about it for now. See y&amp;rsquo;all soon for another post!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~ Lulling &amp;lt;:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
