<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Lyphuriaa on Purple Planetarium</title>
        <link>https://lulullia.github.io/projects/lyphuriaa/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Lyphuriaa on Purple Planetarium</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Lulullia</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lulullia.github.io/projects/lyphuriaa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Peaceful company</title>
        <link>https://lulullia.github.io/entry/2025/art-peaceful-company/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lulullia.github.io/entry/2025/art-peaceful-company/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lulullia.github.io/img/art/peaceful-company.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Peaceful company" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
    &lt;video class=&#34;tumblr-player&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; disablepictureinpicture
         loop autoplay &gt;
        &lt;source src=&#34;https://va.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_sq3907isyB1xjwedr.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
Simply sitting still together, sharing feelings and enjoying the quiet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;timelapse&#34;&gt;Timelapse
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
    &lt;video class=&#34;tumblr-player&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; disablepictureinpicture
        controls   &gt;
        &lt;source src=&#34;https://va.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_sq3a28ZyUX1xjwedr_720.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Vladleen photo</title>
        <link>https://lulullia.github.io/entry/2023/art-vladleen-photo/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 16:59:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lulullia.github.io/entry/2023/art-vladleen-photo/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lulullia.github.io/img/art/vladleen-photo.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Vladleen photo" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Isn’t Lulu so cute? She probably had to beg for days to convince Vlad to make such a cheesy gesture…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;progress-log&#34;&gt;Progress log
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;God this one was especially hard, not really because of what I was drawing but because of &lt;strong&gt;how&lt;/strong&gt;. It made me learn about a bazillion things &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; to repeat &lt;strong&gt;ever&lt;/strong&gt; again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All things considered though, it came out pretty good! I wanted to give up so many times and there were so many catastrophes I’m really surprised in how clean it looks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m even more surprised that I was able to push through and bring it to the finish despite it all, it’s something to celebrate ;-;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lil’ summary of what this piece taught me ⤵&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really need to study the rest of the human anatomy. The legs were difficult, the feet too. I only realize this now because I mostly draw torsos and simple poses. Also, first time I draw characters interacting – it was fun but it’s really something I need to practice more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If I plan on using the sketch as lineart, please for the love of God use an opaque brush. The amount of time I spent fixing the lineart because it was semi-transparent, I might as well have drawn 3 layers of proper lineart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep an eye on the background color. Because of some transparency stuff, I didn’t realize some parts of the drawing only looked right with the current bg color – so when I thought I was done and changed it, I stared in horror at the ugly artifacts all around the drawing. It was painful to fix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sometimes it’s easier to just draw over the sketch, taking the lines I like, instead of cleaning it up. Because using the sketch layer – especially with an opacity brush – leaves around a ton of barely visible artifacts. I had to “select opaque” to see them and clear them out, and it was also painful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generally, going into a drawing without a plan for what style it’s gonna be is a bad idea and results in a lot of problems down the line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Better fix any problems I have with the drawing as early as possible, because I’ll end up fixing it anyway, only if I’m too far in the process it’ll cost me more time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I need to stop drawing too detailed an anatomy if I know it’s gonna get covered by clothes anyway… T-T&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phew, I’m still shocked that I managed to make a decent piece even after all these problems. Somehow I feel pretty good about it, I think the joy of seeing it finished made all my bad experience with it go away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s great, especially since I’ve been struggling a lot with self-doubt about my creative projects recently; this shows me that no matter how crappy something seems to be, if only I push through and finish it, all that bad energy turns into incredibly good feelings of accomplishment and pride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope that’s useful; now I really want to make a mini story game and see how it turns out…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Lulu bust</title>
        <link>https://lulullia.github.io/entry/2022/art-lulu-bust/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 17:34:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lulullia.github.io/entry/2022/art-lulu-bust/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lulullia.github.io/img/art/lulu-bust.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Lulu bust" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m so happy with this one. Not only it’s good to finish a piece, but I also learned how to render with it. I followed a tut and it’s not so hard after all x)&lt;br&gt;
I was mostly focused on anatomy up until now, and I’m excited to switch the focus of my art studies to color, lighting and rendering!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
