<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Artblog on Purple Planetarium</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/blog/art/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Artblog on Purple Planetarium</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Lulling</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 20:42:15 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lullinglore.github.io/blog/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Vladleen duo</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/vladleen-duo/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 20:42:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/vladleen-duo/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/251101.png" alt="Featured image of post Vladleen duo" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m still around~ and Vladleen drawing! &lt;em&gt;(scroll for timelapse)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a while, I&amp;rsquo;m glad to have something new to share today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may look like this account is dead or that I&amp;rsquo;ve vanished, but the truth is that it&amp;rsquo;s normal – drawing is not all that I do, but it&amp;rsquo;s all I can share for now, so that&amp;rsquo;s why there are long stretches of nothing between bursts of posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I work on worldbuilding, story development/writing, and programming when I don&amp;rsquo;t draw, and it&amp;rsquo;s a bit difficult to share that (text is not very attractive + spoilers for the games).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m trying to find ways to have more consistent content to share, hopefully that works out. Due to an illness I have limited energy each day and I&amp;rsquo;d rather focus it all on my stories and games than drawing for social media, that&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s hard to find a balance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I wanted to be clear on why there&amp;rsquo;s often no activity on my accounts, and that it&amp;rsquo;s never because I gave up on my projects. I&amp;rsquo;m just very slow, but no matter what I always come back c:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Lulling / lullinglore:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to change into a new username online and I was supposed to announce that at the same time as another big thing but, looks like I gotta do it earlier than expected c&#39;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll probably do a separate announcement for it later with some more info but I have already secured the new handle &lt;strong&gt;@lullinglore&lt;/strong&gt; everywhere, and I&amp;rsquo;m keeping Lulullia as display name for now to avoid confusion (I&amp;rsquo;ll permanently transition to Lulling some time later).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From now on all my drawings will have the new signature too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for being here and I&amp;rsquo;d love to say hello on socials~ I&amp;rsquo;m patiently but excitedly waiting for the day I can share my first narrative game with everyone * v * in the meantime, have a beautiful day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;timelapse&#34;&gt;Timelapse
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
    &lt;video class=&#34;tumblr-player&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; disablepictureinpicture
        controls   &gt;
        &lt;source src=&#34;https://va.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_t656l7Ag0L1xjwedr.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Orrion Characters #2 ~ Ava</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/orrion-characters-2-ava/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 15:50:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/orrion-characters-2-ava/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/250601.png" alt="Featured image of post Orrion Characters #2 ~ Ava" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ava ~ Blind devotion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Skilled with the spear and with a tongue as sharp as her blade, this headstrong, gossip-loving kitsune escaped life as a royal family relative back on Krakenspire, to the sweet comfort and freedom of the Dolphilie. She settled in Hye&amp;rsquo;s manor after meeting Lurleen, officially working as her bodyguard; but everybody can see the powerful sisterly love bonding these two. Things start going south as Vladimir shows up – the worst person to put in front of Ava – and it&amp;rsquo;s only a matter of time before the bomb goes off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tried new things – it went in a more graphic style this time. I like the effect on this piece, but I think I prefer the softer feel of the [[Orrion Characters 1 ~ Lurleen|previous one]]. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to render my drawings because I don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy the process of painting, but it&amp;rsquo;s still nice to have a quick shaded effect, so I probably won&amp;rsquo;t make more pieces in this clean coloring style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, adding text is super fun and adds so much to the whole thing. I really ought to sort my fonts tho, scrolling a list for 30 minutes trying out every single one is not scaleable at all x)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;timelapse&#34;&gt;Timelapse
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
    &lt;video class=&#34;tumblr-player&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; disablepictureinpicture
        controls   &gt;
        &lt;source src=&#34;https://va.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_sxwmidhvkC1xjwedr_720.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Luli the Jelli</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/luli-the-jelli/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 11:21:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/luli-the-jelli/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/250102.png" alt="Featured image of post Luli the Jelli" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am officially a jellyfish now °v°&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luli the jelli. &lt;del&gt;actually this sounds pretty nice&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wish there was a jelly emoji, but alas, will have to make-do with this 💦&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end I decided to use a cropped version as actual profile pic :c I&amp;rsquo;m sad but it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to have it look like something that can be recognized as a jellyfish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which I guess made me learn that… you should always preview your art in the context in which it&amp;rsquo;ll be used asap… &lt;del&gt;(yea i&amp;rsquo;ll just pretend i didn&amp;rsquo;t already know this and didn&amp;rsquo;t do it out of sheer lazyness)&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other news! Major announcement to come soon. I&amp;rsquo;m preparing something that I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to share but,,, not yet. This is why there have been no posts on socials these days. Even this new profile pic is part of the project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you&amp;rsquo;ll stick around to see it! 🔥&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;timelapse&#34;&gt;Timelapse
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
    &lt;video class=&#34;tumblr-player&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; disablepictureinpicture
        controls   &gt;
        &lt;source src=&#34;https://va.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_sx87iiOEvK1xjwedr_720.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Orrion Characters #1 ~ Lurleen</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/orrion-characters-1-lurleen/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:36:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/orrion-characters-1-lurleen/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/250501.png" alt="Featured image of post Orrion Characters #1 ~ Lurleen" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lurleen ~ Clawed innocence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A loving and spontaneous young woman with the big dream of restoring her and her people&amp;rsquo;s long lost home – Lyphuriaa. Softspoken, emotional and highly sensitive to what goes on between the lines, she lacks a great deal of real-world experience, partly thanks to her amnesia; when Vladimir found her, she was thirteen and didn&amp;rsquo;t even remember her name. Now a distinguished lady under Lord Hye&amp;rsquo;s care, and with Vlad back at her side, Lurleen is ready to fight for her place in this world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very proud of this one. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how, because I never draw, but my lines got so much better, and linework in general. I think I was working against myself before when I tried doing lineart on top of an already good-looking sketch; maybe that&amp;rsquo;s why I always dreaded the lineart phase. It just sucked out all the personality of the sketch. Now I use the sketch as lineart, and I feel way more joy drawing this way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I&amp;rsquo;m in love with the basic round brush with opacity. Literally the only brush I use to draw (but not render). It has such a nice soft look to it! And is very pleasant to use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This piece took way longer than I expected though, and to think I was planning on finishing ones like this every 2-3 days… Well, maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll get faster over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, excited for the next one &lt;del&gt;(spoiler: it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be Vlad [edit: well guess not])&lt;/del&gt; c:&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;timelapse&#34;&gt;Timelapse
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
    &lt;video class=&#34;tumblr-player&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; disablepictureinpicture
        controls   &gt;
        &lt;source src=&#34;https://va.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_swodqaLhPy1xjwedr_720.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ponytail Lulu</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/ponytail-lulu/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 17:42:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/ponytail-lulu/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/250401.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Ponytail Lulu" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lulu c:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been months and I really expected nothing but it came out so great still! Maybe because it&amp;rsquo;s a simpler subject? Drawing busts is pretty easy and fun, will do that more. Also, playing around with effects and textures at the end was interesting – I tried copying some techniques I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in gorgeous artworks from games I play, and it turned out really good!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;timelapse&#34;&gt;Timelapse
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
    &lt;video class=&#34;tumblr-player&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; disablepictureinpicture
        controls   &gt;
        &lt;source src=&#34;https://va.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_swgv2mNEtf1xjwedr_720.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Peaceful company</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/peaceful-company/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2025/peaceful-company/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/250101.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Peaceful company" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
    &lt;video class=&#34;tumblr-player&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; disablepictureinpicture
         loop autoplay &gt;
        &lt;source src=&#34;https://va.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_sq3907isyB1xjwedr.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
Simply sitting still together, sharing feelings and enjoying the quiet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;timelapse&#34;&gt;Timelapse
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
    &lt;video class=&#34;tumblr-player&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; disablepictureinpicture
        controls   &gt;
        &lt;source src=&#34;https://va.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_sq3a28ZyUX1xjwedr_720.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Vladleen photo</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2023/vladleen-photo/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 16:59:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2023/vladleen-photo/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/230602.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Vladleen photo" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lulu probably had to beg for days to convince Vlad to make such a cheesy gesture…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;follow-up-drawing&#34;&gt;Follow-up drawing
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few kind persons gave me a shout-out over on Game Jolt and a lot of new people came to follow my account – so I made a small thank you drawing &amp;lt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/230602_1.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;2048&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;148&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;356px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;progress-log&#34;&gt;Progress log
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;God this one was especially hard, not really because of what I was drawing but because of &lt;strong&gt;how&lt;/strong&gt;. It made me learn about a bazillion things &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; to repeat &lt;strong&gt;ever&lt;/strong&gt; again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All things considered though, it came out pretty good! I wanted to give up so many times and there were so many catastrophes I’m really surprised in how clean it looks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m even more surprised that I was able to push through and bring it to the finish despite it all, it’s something to celebrate ;-;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lil’ summary of what this piece taught me ⤵&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really need to study the rest of the human anatomy. The legs were difficult, the feet too. I only realize this now because I mostly draw torsos and simple poses. Also, first time I draw characters interacting – it was fun but it’s really something I need to practice more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If I plan on using the sketch as lineart, please for the love of God use an opaque brush. The amount of time I spent fixing the lineart because it was semi-transparent, I might as well have drawn 3 layers of proper lineart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep an eye on the background color. Because of some transparency stuff, I didn’t realize some parts of the drawing only looked right with the current bg color – so when I thought I was done and changed it, I stared in horror at the ugly artifacts all around the drawing. It was painful to fix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sometimes it’s easier to just draw over the sketch, taking the lines I like, instead of cleaning it up. Because using the sketch layer – especially with an opacity brush – leaves around a ton of barely visible artifacts. I had to “select opaque” to see them and clear them out, and it was also painful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generally, going into a drawing without a plan for what style it’s gonna be is a bad idea and results in a lot of problems down the line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Better fix any problems I have with the drawing as early as possible, because I’ll end up fixing it anyway, only if I’m too far in the process it’ll cost me more time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I need to stop drawing too detailed an anatomy if I know it’s gonna get covered by clothes anyway… T-T&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phew, I’m still shocked that I managed to make a decent piece even after all these problems. Somehow I feel pretty good about it, I think the joy of seeing it finished made all my bad experience with it go away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s great, especially since I’ve been struggling a lot with self-doubt about my creative projects recently; this shows me that no matter how crappy something seems to be, if only I push through and finish it, all that bad energy turns into incredibly good feelings of accomplishment and pride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope that’s useful; now I really want to make a mini story game and see how it turns out…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nom bust</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2023/nom-bust/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:50:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2023/nom-bust/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/230224.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Nom bust" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;First character portrait from Project Circus featuring Nom, the youngest member of the crew!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She has the unsettling habit of always munching on her fingers, despite the collective efforts of the other members to make her stop. But if she finds herself unable to remove the bandages on her hands, Nom won&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to search for another collection of soft fingers to feast on…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Lulu bust</title>
        <link>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2022/lulu-bust/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 17:34:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://lullinglore.github.io/entry/2022/lulu-bust/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://lullinglore.github.io/img/art/220101.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Lulu bust" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m so happy with this one. Not only it’s good to finish a piece, but I also learned how to render with it. I followed a tut and it’s not so hard after all x)&lt;br&gt;
I was mostly focused on anatomy up until now, and I’m excited to switch the focus of my art studies to color, lighting and rendering!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
